Guide to the Boone and Crockett Club Records circa 1885-2009
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
- Administration, 1888-2007; Series I; 45.5 linear feet
  - Membership, 1899-2007; Subseries 6; 6.50 linear feet
    - Membership Directory, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 66/1)
    - Membership Directory, Correspondence, 1974 (Box-folder 66/2)
    - Membership Directory, Inventory, undated (Box-folder 66/3)
    - Membership Endorsements, 1928-1940 (Box-folder 66/4-6)
    - Membership Endorsements, 1956-1958 (Box-folder 66/7)
    - Membership Endorsements, 1983-1991 (Box-folder 66/8)
    - Membership Form Letters, 1965-1974 (Box-folder 66/9)
    - Membership Form Letters, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 66/10)
    - Membership Forms, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 66/11)
    - Membership Inquiries, 1961-1976 (Box-folder 66/12)
    - Membership Inquiries, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 66/13)
    - Membership Inquiries, Form Response Letters, 1962-1974 (Box-folder 66/14)
    - Membership List by State, undated (Box-folder 66/15)
    - Membership Military Questionnaire, 1941-1945 (Box-folder 66/16)
    - Membership Qualification Changes, 1942 (Box-folder 66/17)
    - Membership, Resignations and Transfers, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 66/18)
    - Membership Resignations, 1992 (Box-folder 66/19)
    - Membership Sponsors Lists, 1988 (Box-folder 66/20)
    - Nominating Committee, Correspondence, 1908 (Box-folder 66/21)
    - Nominating Committee, Correspondence and Reports, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 66/22)
    - Nominating Committee, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1973-1983 (Box-folder 66/23)
    - Nominating Committee, Reports, 1949-1980 (Box-folder 66/24)
    - Officers, Constitution and List of Members Booklets, 1906 (Box-folder 67/1)
    - Officers, Constitution and List of Members Booklets, 1910 (Box-folder 234/5)
    - Officers, Constitution and List of Members Booklets, 1911 (Box-folder 67/2)
    - Officers, Constitution and List of Members Booklets, 1914 (Box-folder 67/3)
    - Officers, Constitution, Report of Game Preservation Committee, and List of Members Booklets, 1915 (Box-folder 67/4)
    - Officers, Constitution, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1916 (Box-folder 67/5)
    - Officers, Constitution, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1917 (Box-folder 67/6)
    - Officers, Constitution, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1918-1919 (Box-folder 67/7)
    - Officers, Constitution, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 67/8)
    - Officers, Constitution, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1920-1921 (Box-folder 67/9)
    - Officers, Constitution, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1921-1922 (Box-folder 67/10)
    - Officers, Constitution, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1922-1923 (Box-folder 67/11)
    - Officers, Constitution, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 67/12)
    - Officers, Constitution, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1924-1925 (Box-folder 67/13)
    - Officers, Constitution, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 67/14)
    - Officers, Constitution, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1926-1927 (Box-folder 68/1)
    - Officers, Constitution, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1927-1928 (Box-folder 68/2)
    - Officers, Constitution, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1929-1930 (Box-folder 68/3)
    - Officers, Constitution, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1930-1931 (Box-folder 68/4)
    - Officers, Constitution, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1931-1932 (Box-folder 68/5)
    - Officers, Constitution, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1932-1933 (Box-folder 68/6)
    - Officers, Constitution, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 68/7)
    - Officers, Constitution, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 68/8)
    - Officers, Constitution, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 234/6)
    - Officers, Constitution, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 68/9)
    - Officers, Constitution, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 68/10)
    - Officers, By-Laws, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 68/11)
    - Officers, By-Laws, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 69/1)
    - Officers, By-Laws, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1940-1942 (Box-folder 69/2)
    - Officers, By-Laws, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1941-1943 (Box-folder 69/3)
    - Officers, By-Laws, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1943-1946 (Box-folder 69/4)
    - Officers, By-Laws, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1947 (Box-folder 69/5)
    - Officers, By-Laws, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 69/6)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1951 (Box-folder 69/7)
    - Officers, By-Laws, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1953 (Box-folder 69/8)
    - Officers, By-Laws, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 69/9)
    - Officers, By-Laws, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1955 (Box-folder 69/10)
    - Officers, By-Laws, Treasurer's Report, and List of Members Booklets, 1957 (Box-folder 70/1)
    - Officers, By-Laws, Assets and Liabilities, and Lists of Members Booklets, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 70/2)
    - Officers, By-Laws, Assets and Liabilities, and Lists of Members Booklets, 1961 (Box-folder 70/3)
    - Officers, By-Laws, Assets and Liabilities, and Lists of Members Booklets, 1963 (Box-folder 70/4)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1969 (Box-folder 70/5)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1971 (Box-folder 70/6)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1972 (Box-folder 70/7)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1973 (Box-folder 70/8)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1974 (Box-folder 70/9)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1975 (Box-folder 70/10)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1976 (Box-folder 70/11)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 70/12)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1978 (Box-folder 70/13)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1979 (Box-folder 70/14)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1980 (Box-folder 70/15)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1981 (Box-folder 70/16)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1982 (Box-folder 70/17)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1983 (Box-folder 70/18)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1984 (Box-folder 70/19)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1985 (Box-folder 71/1)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1986 (Box-folder 71/2)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1987 (Box-folder 71/3)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1988 (Box-folder 71/4)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1991 (Box-folder 71/5)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1993 (Box-folder 71/6)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1994 (Box-folder 71/7)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 71/8)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 71/9)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 71/10)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 71/11)
    - Officers, By-Laws, List of Members Booklets, 2000 (Box-folder 71/12)
    - Officers, By-Laws, and List of Members, 2001 (Box-folder 229/12)
    - Officers, By-Laws, and List of Members, 2002 (Box-folder 229/11)
    - Officers, By-Laws, and List of Members, 2003 (Box-folder 229/10)
    - Officers, By-Laws, and List of Members, 2004 (Box-folder 228/5)
    - Officers, By-Laws, and List of Members, 2006 (Box-folder 229/1)
    - Officers, By-Laws, and List of Members, 2007 (Box-folder 228/4)
    - Marco Pastrana, Membership Candidacy, 1991 (Box-folder 227/9)
    - Professional Members, White Paper, Memorandum, 1998 (Box-folder 72/1)
    - Proposals for Membership, 1899-1906 (Box-folder 72/2)
    - Proposals for Membership, 1920 (Box-folder 72/3)
    - Proposals for Membership, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 72/4)
    - Proposals for Membership, 1998 (Box-folder 72/5)
    - Proposed Club Expansion, Correspondence, 1901 (Box-folder 72/6)
    - Proposed New Members, Biographical Information, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 72/7)
    - Prospective Member Materials and Proposals, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 72/8)
    - Prospective Member Packet, circa 2000 (Box-folder 72/9)
    - Prospective Member Packet, 2005-2005 (Box-folder 228/10)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1912 (Box-folder 72/10)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1913 (Box-folder 72/11)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1914 (Box-folder 72/12)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1915 (Box-folder 72/13)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1917 (Box-folder 72/14)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1918 (Box-folder 72/15)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1919 (Box-folder 72/16)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1920 (Box-folder 72/17)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1921 (Box-folder 72/18)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1922 (Box-folder 72/19)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1923 (Box-folder 72/20)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1925 (Box-folder 72/21)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1926 (Box-folder 72/22)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1927 (Box-folder 72/23)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1930 (Box-folder 72/24)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1933 (Box-folder 72/25)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballots, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 234/7)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1935 (Box-folder 72/26)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1982 (Box-folder 72/27)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1991 (Box-folder 72/28)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1992 (Box-folder 72/29)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1993 (Box-folder 72/30)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1994 (Box-folder 72/31)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1995 (Box-folder 72/32)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1996 (Box-folder 72/33)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1997 (Box-folder 73/1)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1998 (Box-folder 73/2)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot, 1999 (Box-folder 73/3)
    - Regular Membership, Election Ballot Information, 1992 (Box-folder 73/4)
    - Reports to Membership, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 73/5)
    - Theodore Roosevelt, List of Membership Notations, 1901 and undated (Box-folder 73/6)
    - Sponsors for Current Members, 1985 (Box-folder 73/7)
    - Tilghman Membership, Correspondence, 1901 (Box-folder 73/8)
    - Philip Wright, Honorary Life Membership, Correspondence and Meeting Materials, 1985 (Box-folder 73/9)
  - Library, 1960-1984; Subseries 7; 0.5 linear feet
    This subseries contains correspondence, appraisals, and inventories pertaining to the Club library that contains materials owned by the Roosevelt family and gifted to the Club by other members.
    - Appraisal, 1976 (Box-folder 73/10-11)
    - Book Purchases, 1971 (Box-folder 73/12)
    - Childs Frick Library Legacy, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 73/13)
    - Correspondence, Inventories, and Memoranda, 1965-1978 (Box-folder 73/14)
    - Editorial and Historical Committee, Library Questionnaire, 1984 (Box-folder 73/15)
    - Editorial and Historical Committee, Report on Carnegie Library Books, 1960-1974 (Box-folder 73/16)
    - Historical and Publicity Committee, Frick Collection Books, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 73/17)
    - Inventory of Books for Sale, 1975 (Box-folder 73/18)
    - Inventory of Library at the Carnegie Museum, undated (Box-folder 73/19 (1 of 2))
    - Inventory of Library at the Carnegie Museum, undated (Box-folder 74/1 (2 of 2))
    - Transfer of Boone and Crockett Library to Carnegie Museum, 1978 (Box-folder 74/2)
  - Physical Assets, 1910-2002; Subseries 8; 2.75 linear feet
    This subseries includes correspondence, committee materials and minutes, inventories and materials and plans related to the purchase and remodel of the Old Milwaukee Railroad Depot (the Club’s current headquarters in Missoula, Montana). Of possible interest in this series are materials documenting the ownership of Guns gifted to the Club by the Roosevelt family and currently stored at the Sagamore Hill National Historic Site in Oyster Bay, New York.
    - Bob Marcotte Gun, Correspondence, 1991 (Box-folder 74/3)
    - Daniel Boone Rifle, Correspondence, 1910 (Box-folder 74/4)
    - Firearms, Correspondence, and Memoranda, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 74/5)
    - Firearms and Collectables Trust, Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 74/6)
    - Firearms and Collectables Trust, Pamphlet, 1995 (Box-folder 74/7)
    - Hunting Rifles Held for the Boone and Crockett Club by George Bird Grinnell, Correspondence, 1911-1912 and undated (Box-folder 74/8)
    - Inventory and Audit of Communities Considered by the Boone and Crockett Club for Headquarters Relocation, 1992 (Box-folder 74/9)
    - List of Guns belonging to the Boone and Crockett Club, 1916 (Box-folder 74/10)
    - Old Milwaukee Depot, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 74/11-12)
    - Old Milwaukee Depot Committee, Certificate of Survey, 1990 (Box-folder 74/13)
    - Old Milwaukee Depot Committee, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 74/14)
    - Old Milwaukee Depot Committee, Floor Plans, 1993 (Box-folder 74/15)
    - Old Milwaukee Depot Floor Plans, Perspective Sketches, Restoration and Repair Scope, 1993 (Box-folder OS 223/x)
    - Old Milwaukee Depot Fund, Fiscal Year 1996, Budget and Financial Statements, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 74/16)
    - Old Milwaukee Depot Fund, Fiscal Year 1997, Budget and Financial Statements, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 74/17)
    - Old Milwaukee Depot, Interior Renovation Plans, 2003 (Box-folder OS 224/1)
    - Old Milwaukee Depot Renovation, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1993 (Box-folder 75/1)
    - Old Milwaukee Depot, Missoula, Montana, Lease, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 75/2)
    - Old Milwaukee Depot, National Register of Historic Places Nomination, 1980 (Box-folder 75/3)
    - Old Milwaukee Depot, Schematic Floor Plan, 1994 (Box-folder OS 224/2)
    - Permanent Records in Pittsburgh, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1974 (Box-folder 75/4)
    - Press Release, undated (Box-folder 75/5)
    - Property, Receipts and Correspondence, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 75/6)
    - Archibald Roosevelt, Gun and Book Inventory, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 75/7)
    - Theodore Roosevelt Guns, Photographs, 1974 (Box-folder 75/8)
    - Theodore Roosevelt Guns, Photographs, undated (Box-folder 75/9)
    - Theodore Roosevelt Guns, Sagamore Hill National Historic Site, Correspondence, 1993 (Box-folder 75/10)
    - Theodore Roosevelt Rifle, Loan to the National Rifle Association, 1971-1984 (Box-folder 75/11)
    - Sagamore Hill Committee, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1949-1959 (Box-folder 75/12-13)
    - Sagamore Hill Committee, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1950-1969 (Box-folder 75/14-15 (1-2 of 3))
    - Sagamore Hill Committee, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1950-1969 (Box-folder 76/1 (3 of 3))
    - Sagamore Hill Committee, Correspondence and Reports, 1963-1972 (Box-folder 76/2)
    - Sagamore Hill Committee, Correspondence, Memoranda, and Reports, 1973-1980 (Box-folder 76/3)
    - Sagamore Hill Committee, Reports, 1963-1993 (Box-folder 76/4)
    - Sagamore Hill Committee, Carl Rungius Paintings, Correspondence and Meeting Minutes, 1954-1973 (Box-folder 76/5)
    - Sagamore Hill National Historic Site, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1987-1995 (Box-folder 76/6-7)
    - Sagamore Hill, Correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box-folder 76/8-11)
    - Sagamore Hill, Correspondence, 1955-1972 (Box-folder 77/1)
    - Sagamore Hill, Correspondence, 1972-1998 (Box-folder 77/2)
    - Sagamore Hill, Furnishings, Correspondence, 1952-1961 (Box-folder 77/3)
    - Sagamore Hill, Game Head Correspondence, 1954-1960 (Box-folder 77/4)
    - Sagamore Hill, Grizzly Rug, Permit, 1982 (Box-folder 77/5)
    - Sagamore Hill, Gun Controversy, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1995 (Box-folder 77/6)
    - Sagamore Hill, Gun Room, Correspondence, 1952-1966 (Box-folder 77/7)
    - Sagamore Hill, Gun Room, Report of Contents, 1959 (Box-folder 77/8)
    - Sagamore Hill, Guns, Case for Boone and Crockett Club Ownership, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 77/9)
    - Sagamore Hill, Guns, John W. Hanes, Jr., Correspondence, 1995 (Box-folder 77/10)
    - Sagamore Hill, Guns, Insurance Policy for Rifles, 1999 (Box-folder 77/11)
    - Sagamore Hill, Guns, Inventories, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 77/12)
    - Sagamore Hill, Guns, Members Only Sale, 1972 (Box-folder 78/1)
    - Sagamore Hill, Guns, National Park Service, Loan Agreement, 1991-1998 (Box-folder 78/2)
    - Sagamore Hill, Inventory, 1955-1995 (Box-folder 78/3)
    - Sagamore Hill, Inventories, 1963-2000 (Box-folder 78/4)
    - Sagamore Hill, Inventory, undated (Box-folder 78/5)
    - Sagamore Hill, Inventories and Receipts for Items Shipped to Missoula, 2000 (Box-folder 78/6)
    - Sagamore Hill, Inventory, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1951-1991 (Box-folder 78/7-9)
    - Sagamore Hill, Inventory, Sherman Gray, Affidavit, 1994 (Box-folder 79/1)
    - Sagamore Hill, National Park Service, Correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 79/2)
    - Sagamore Hill, Related Committee Meeting Minutes, 1951-1973 (Box-folder 79/3)
    - Sagamore Hill, Research on History, 1950-1991 (Box-folder 79/4)
    - Sagamore Hill, Marie Rust, Correspondence, 1995 (Box-folder 79/5)
    - Sagamore Hill, Sherman Gray, Correspondence, 1995-2002 (Box-folder 225/3)
    - Sagamore Hill, Theodore Roosevelt Association, Correspondence, 1995 (Box-folder 79/6)
  - History, 1912-1999; Subseries 9; 0.75 linear feet
    This subseries contains committee minutes, correspondence, and materials related to various unpublished histories written about the Club. This subseries also contains materials related to the Oral History project started by the Club to document its history through interviews with longtime members.
    - Club History, Dr. Richard Derby, 1951 and undated (Box-folder 234/8)
    - Club History, Invoice, 1912 (Box-folder 79/7)
    - Club History Manuscripts, undated (Box-folder 79/8)
    - Club History, Richard E. McCabe Revisions, Correspondence, 1988 (Box-folder 79/9)
    - Committee on Club History, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1957-1961 (Box-folder 79/10)
    - Correspondence, 1953-1961 (Box-folder 79/11-12)
    - Historical Committee, Correspondence, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 79/13)
    - Historical Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 79/14)
    - Historical Committee, Reports, 1973 (Box-folder 79/15)
    - Historical Material and Contacts, 1978 (Box-folder 80/1)
    - Oral History Project, 1983 (Box-folder 80/2)
    - Oral History Project, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 80/3)
    - Oral History Project, Interview Cards and Questions, 1978 (Box 221)
    - Oral History Project, Interview List, undated (Box-folder 80/4)
    - Oral History Project, John E. Rhea Interview Transcript, 1977 (Box-folder 80/5)
    - Oral History Project, Project Summary, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 80/6-7)
    - Oral History Project, Synopsis of Work Completed, 1996 (Box-folder 80/8)
  - Speeches and Dedications, 1919-1975; Subseries 10; 0.1 linear feet
    This subseries includes drafts and copies of dedications, eulogies, speeches, and other statements given by Club members.
    - Dedications, 1921-1927 (Box-folder 80/9)
    - Member Eulogies, 1919 and undated (Box-folder 80/10)
    - John E. Rhea, Statement to Club for American Rifleman, 1968 (Box-folder 80/11)
    - Speeches, 1919 and undated (Box-folder 80/12)
    - Major William Austin Wadsworth, Eulogy, Club Booklet, 1919 (Box-folder 80/13)
    - Lawrence C. Woods, Dedication to Elk Group at the Carnegie Museum, 1975 (Box-folder 80/14)
  - Office Administration, 1958-1995; Subseries 11; 1.375 linear feet
    This subseries is divided into two sub-subseries and documents the administration of Club offices.
    - General Materials, 1958-1995; Sub-subseries 1; 0.875 linear feet
      Sub sub-series 1 includes office policies, stationary, general inquiries and other materials related to office administration. Of particular interest in this sub-subseries are folders that document the move of the Club’s headquarters from Pittsburgh to Virginia and from Virginia to Montana.
      - Committee List, circa 1988 (Box-folder 80/15)
      - Conference Room Leasing Contracts, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 80/16)
      - Contact File, 1989 (Box-folder 80/17)
      - Contracts and Job Descriptions, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 80/18)
      - Dumfries, Virginia Lease Agreement, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 80/19)
      - E.O.G. 2000 LST, Incorporated, Lease Agreement, 1994 (Box-folder 80/20)
      - Facility Use, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 80/21)
      - Form Letters, 1965-1973 (Box-folder 80/22)
      - Form Letters, Miscellaneous, undated (Box-folder 81/1)
      - Forms, Originals, 1981 and undated (Box-folder 81/2)
      - General Inquiries, 1977 (Box-folder 81/3)
      - General Inquiries, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 81/4)
      - Glacier Park Company, Agency and Tenancy Agreement, 1992 (Box-folder 81/5)
      - Guestbook, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 81/6)
      - Guestbook, 1993 (Box-folder 81/7)
      - Independent Contractor Contract, undated (Box-folder 81/8)
      - Information Inquiries, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 81/9)
      - Letterhead, Negatives and Proofs, undated (Box-folder 81/10)
      - Line Art and Logo, 1988 and undated (Box-folder 81/11)
      - Luggage Tag, Negatives, undated (Box-folder 81/12)
      - Mailing List Acquisition, 1988 (Box-folder 81/13)
      - Lawrence Means, Trip Report, 1991 (Box-folder 81/14)
      - Montana Annual Corporation Report, 1994 (Box-folder 81/15)
      - Office Administrator, Job Description, 1980 (Box-folder 81/16)
      - Office and Miscellaneous Originals, 1989-1992 and undated (Box-folder 81/17)
      - Office Lease, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 81/18)
      - Office Location, Correspondence and Floor Plan, 1985 (Box-folder 81/19)
      - Office Policy, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 81/20)
      - Offices, Move From Virginia to Montana, 1992 (Box-folder 81/21)
      - Offices, Move to Washington from Pittsburgh, 1975 (Box-folder 81/22)
      - Offices, Move to Washington from Pittsburgh, Correspondence, 1975-1981 (Box-folder 81/23)
      - Personnel, Office Instructions, 1966-1975 (Box-folder 82/1)
      - Pittsburgh Office, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 82/2)
      - Secretarial Duties, 1958-1961 (Box-folder 82/3)
      - Stationary, undated (Box-folder 82/4)
      - Stationary, undated (Box-folder 82/5)
      - Stationary and Letterhead, 1974 and undated (Box-folder 82/6)
      - Stationary Requirements, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 82/7)
      - Stationary, Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 82/8)
    - Staff Correspondence, 1968-1992; Sub-subseries 2; 0.5 linear feet